if you're new to graphic design then you
如果你是平面设计新手，那么你
may be unfamiliar with what the
可能不熟悉的是
different types of design are why
不同类型的设计是为什么
they're used and how they're made in
它们是如何使用的，以及它们是如何制造的
this video I'll be giving you a brief
这段视频我会给你一个简短的
overview of what Vector design is in
什么是向量设计概述
particular and how you can use inkscape
特定以及如何使用Inkscape
to create
创造
[Music]
[音乐]
it this is Nick with logos by nick.com
我是尼克，Nick.com的徽标
and today I'll be explaining how
今天我将向你解释
inkscape Works in 5 minutes or less
Inkscape在5分钟或更短的时间内即可工作
inkscape is a free an open source vector
Inkscape是一个免费的开源载体
graphics editor similar to Adobe
类似于Adobe的图形编辑器
Illustrator the graphical format you may
Illustrator图形格式，您可以
be most familiar with would probably be
最熟悉的可能是
the raster format where you're working
您正在使用的栅格格式
with a bunch of individual colored boxes
用一堆单独的彩色盒子
known as pixels this describes things
称为像素，它描述的是事物
like photographs and jpeg images vector
像照片和jpeg图像向量
graphics aren't made of pixels though
不过，图形不是由像素组成的
they're a series of mathematical
它们是一系列的数学运算
equations that dictate the properties of
决定属性的方程式
a graphic on an X Andy AIS the benefit
安迪X上的一个图形就是好处
of working with vector graphics is that
使用矢量图形的最大优点是
they're easier to manipulate and you can
它们更容易操纵，你可以
enlarge them infin itely without quality
无质量地无限放大它们
loss this makes vectors ideal for things
损失这使矢量成为事物的理想选择
like logos and app icons where you'll
比如徽标和应用程序图标，在那里你将
need to use the same design in a variety
需要在不同的产品中使用相同的设计
of different sizes vector graphics can
不同大小的矢量图形可以
also be used to create things like
也可用于创建类似于
characters and mascots digital
数字角色和吉祥物
illustrations menu icons for the web and
Web和的插图菜单图标
they can even be used in combination
它们甚至可以组合使用
with raster images to create
要创建的栅格图像
advertisements headers for social media
社交媒体的广告标题
or anything else you'd like my favorite
或者其他你喜欢的东西，我最喜欢的
tool for creating vector graphics is
创建矢量图形的工具是
inkscape and on this channel you'll find
Inkscape和在这个频道上你会发现
hundreds of tutorials for learning how
学习方法的数百个教程
to use inkscape to create things like
要使用Inkscape创建类似于
logos icons posters textures and more
徽标、图标、海报、纹理等
when you launch inkscape for the first
当您第一次启动Inkscape时
time after downloading it you may notice
下载后的时间您可能会注意到
that it doesn't quite look the same on
它看起来不太一样
your screen as it does on mine when
你的屏幕就像我的屏幕一样
following along with one of my tutorials
下面是我的一篇教程
you can change this by going to edit
您可以通过转到编辑来更改此设置
preferences interface and theme and
首选项界面和主题以及
ticking on the boxes to use a dark theme
在方框上打勾以使用黑色主题
along with the symbolic icons this is
连同符号图标一起，这是
not something that's necessary but it
不是什么必要的东西，但它
just may be easier for you to follow
只是可能更容易让你跟上
along Ong with my lessons if things look
如果事情看起来像是继续我的课程
the same on your screen as they do on
屏幕上显示的内容与屏幕上的相同
mine the tools menu on the left hand
我在左手上的工具菜单中
side of the screen allows you to create
屏幕的一侧允许您创建
Vector objects like squares circles
像正方形圆一样的矢量对象
stars and polygons and you can even use
星形和多边形，你甚至可以使用
tools like the beier pen and the
像贝尔钢笔和
freehand tool to draw your own Vector
用于绘制您自己的矢量的手绘工具
shapes you can then edit the structural
形状，然后您可以编辑结构
properties of those shapes using the
这些形状的属性使用
edit pads by nodes tool which allows you
按节点编辑焊盘工具，允许您
to change the Contours of individual
改变个人轮廓的步骤
lines and the key points of the design
线条与设计要点
otherwise known as nodes you can add
也称为您可以添加的节点
nodes remove nodes and even change the
节点删除节点，甚至更改
type of node you're working with you can
您可以使用的节点类型
then give those shapes whatever color
然后给这些形状赋予任何颜色
you want using the color palette at the
您想要使用调色板在
bottom of the screen or you can choose
屏幕底部或您可以选择
Your Colors by RGB or hex code by
您的颜色按RGB或十六进制代码按
opening up the fill and stroke menu you
打开填充和描边菜单
can even fill your objects with a
甚至可以用一个
gradient which is basically a transition
渐变，基本上是一种过渡
between two different colors the path
在两种不同颜色之间的路径
menu at the top of the screen is a
屏幕顶部的菜单是一个
series of path operations that allows
一系列路径操作，允许
you to take objects that you've already
你要把你已经拥有的东西
created and turn them into new objects
创建并将它们转换为新对象
based on how you make them interact with
基于你如何让他们与
each other you can unify them together
你可以把他们统一在一起
subtract them from each other use the
将它们相减，使用
intersecting area between them to create
它们之间的相交区域以创建
a new object and more there's even a
一个新的物体和更多的东西，甚至还有
more advanced feature known as live path
更高级的功能称为活动路径
effects which allows you to manipulate
允许您操纵的效果
your vector objects even further
您的矢量对象甚至更远
inkscape also has a powerful text editor
Inkscape也有一个功能强大的文本编辑器
built in that allows you to flow text
内置的，允许您流动的文本
inside of objects wrap it around objects
在对象内部将其包裹在对象周围
and even warp it into different shapes
甚至把它扭曲成不同的形状
and there's countless other features in
此外，还有无数其他功能
inkscape that make it a powerful tool
Inkscape使其成为一种强大工具
like texture masking and clone stamping
如纹理遮罩和克隆盖章
once you have a solid understanding of
一旦你对此有了扎实的了解
how all of this works you can create
您可以创建所有这些功能的工作原理
some really impressive designs there
那里有一些非常令人印象深刻的设计
really are no limitations to what you
真的没有限制你做什么
can create with inkscape it's just as
可以使用Inkscape进行创作，就像
powerful as any other vector graphics
与任何其他矢量图形一样强大
tool out there commercial or otherwise
无论是商业工具还是其他工具
I've personally been using inkscape as
我个人一直使用Inkscape作为
my primary tool for over a decade to
我十多年来的主要工具
design logos for my clients and graphics
为我的客户和图形设计标志
for my own website I even have an online
对于我自己的网站，我甚至有一个在线
course called The inkscape Master Class
名为Inkscape大师班的课程
where I go over every single tool and
在那里我检查了每一个工具
feature in inkscape and explain how it
Inkscape中的功能并解释它如何
works it's kind of like a user manual
它有点像是一本用户手册
but in video format where you can ask
但在视频格式中，你可以问
questions and get help from me anytime
任何时候都可以向我提问并寻求帮助
you want and it may be helpful in giving
你想要的，这可能会对你的
some context to my lessons here on
我在这里所学到的一些背景知识
YouTube I'll put a link in the
我会在YouTube上放一个链接
description of the video if you're
视频描述，如果您是
interested in checking that out
有兴趣检查一下吗
otherwise if you're just curious about
否则，如果你只是好奇
seeing what inkscape is capable of and
了解Inkscape的能力和
maybe dabbling around with it a bit then
也许可以稍微试一试
feel free to check out any of the
您可以随时查看任何
hundreds of tutorials I have on this
关于这一点，我有数百个教程
channel I even have a beginners playlist
我频道甚至有一个初学者播放列表
that would be ideal for firsttime users
这对于第一次使用的用户来说将是理想的
if you have any questions just leave a
如果您有任何问题，请在
comment below and as always thanks for
在下面发表评论，并一如既往地感谢
watching for
守候着